Guide to the American Federation of Teachers Local 200 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- American Federation of Teachers Local 200 Records, 1943-1974; 1909-004; 5.42 cubic feet 6 boxes
  - SUBJECT FILES, 1950-1973; SERIES VI (Box-folder 3/8-4/40)
    - Desegregation and Racial Issues, 1967-1971; Subseries D (Box-folder 3/33-4/2)
      - Garfield High School: Curricular and Safety Issues: Correspondence, Memoranda, and Press, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Correspondence and Planning: Desegregation/Integration, 1969 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - Teacher Hiring for Middle Schools, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3/36)
      - Teacher Hiring and Integration Planning for Middle Schools, 1971 (Box-folder 3/37)
      - Racial Distribution, Seattle Public Schools., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 3/38)
      - More Effective Schools Program (1 of 2), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - More Effective Schools Program (2 of 2), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Contract Negotiations and Teacher Benefits, 1950-1971; Subseries E (Box-folder 4/3-4/14)
      - Proposed Constitution and By-Laws of the Snohomish County Labor Council, 1950-1970 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Insurance: Correspondence, Reports and Publications, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Seattle Teachers Association: Contract Negotiations, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Contract Negotiations: Other Teachers' Unions' Contracts and Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers: Contracts and News Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Correspondence: Teacher Exchange, 1969 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Teacher Problem Clinic, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Involuntary Teacher Transfers: Policy and Meetings, 1970 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Teacher Transfer Procedure, 1970 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Insurance, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Contract Negotiations, 1969 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Teacher Contract Negotiations: Contract Stacking, 1969 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - King County Labor Council, 1968-1971; Subseries F (Box-folder 4/15-4/16)
      - King County Labor Council: Correspondence, Proceedings, Minutes, Do Not Patronize List, and Budget Documents, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - King County Labor Council: Proceedings, Press, Financial Reports, Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Legislation and Political Action, 1955-1972; Subseries G (Box-folder 4/17-4/25)
      - Special Levy to Fund Seattle Public Schools (1 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Special Levy to Fund Seattle Public Schools (2 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Correspondence: Seattle Teachers Association to Executive Board Members: Union Challenge and Levy, 1971 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - News Clippings and Correspondence: School Budget Crisis, 1969 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Legislative Committee, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - School Levy 60-40 Challenge, 1970 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - School Levy, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Lawsuit Against Seattle School District to Secure Contracts for Qualified Non-Contract Teachers: Washington State Superior Court Case No. 719016, 1970 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers: Legislation, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Federations of Teachers from Other States, 1968-1970; Subseries H (Box-folder 4/26-4/28)
      - Publications by the Philadelphia and Pennsylvania Federations of Teachers, 1969 (Box-folder 4/26)
      - San Francisco Federation of Teachers, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Denver Federation of Teachers, 1969 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Office Administrative Files, 1963-1971; Subseries I (Box-folder 4/29-4/36)
      - Advertisement: Bell System Electronic Secretary, 1963 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Membership List, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Membership Updating, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Bulk School Mailing: U.S. Postal Service, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Executive Board Telephone Tree, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Membership, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/34)
      - University of Washington Teacher Certification Program, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Correspondence and School Conditions Survey: Seattle Chamber of Commerce, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - School Policy, 1966-1973; Subseries J (Box-folder 4/37-4/40)
      - State Board of Education Rules and Regulations: Sex Education, 1969 (Box-folder 4/37)
      - Statement of Seattle School District No. 1 with Regard to The Use by the Police Department of Undercover Agents in the High Schools: Written by Superintendent Forbes Bottomly, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Press, Correspondence, and Policy: Student Freedom of Expression in Public Schools, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Policies and Staff Everett Federation of Teachers, 1972 (Box-folder 4/40)
  - NEWSPAPERS, 1953-1971; SERIES VII (Box-folder 4/41-5/9)
    - Press on Alternative Schools: The Seattle Times and the Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - News Clippings Related to School Finance: Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1971 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - Washington State Federation of Teachers: Press, Publications, Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Newspaper Clippings (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/44)
    - Newspaper Clippings (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - Press- Letters to the Editor - Seattle Post Intelligencer, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/46)
    - Press Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/47)
    - Article: Seattle Post-Intelligencer: "School Code Can Require Expulsion of Young Rebels", 1969 (Box-folder 4/48)
    - Publication: The Medium, 1970 (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Publication: Seattle Teacher, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Publication: American Teacher, 1969 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Publication: Washington Teacher, 1947-1965 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Newspapers and Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Press: Washington State Federation of Teachers, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Press: Washington State Federation of Teachers, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Publication: Seattle Teacher (1 of 2), 1964-1968 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Publication: Seattle Teacher (2 of 2), 1964-1968 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1953-1960 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS, 1964-1969; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Everett Federation of Teachers: Wil Knutsen Files: Photograph, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - PUBLICATIONS, LEAFLETS, AND ELECTION MATERIALS, 1947-1974; SERIES IX (Box-folder 5/11-6/11)
    - Press, Leaflets, Agendas and Resolutions/Amendments: The 1971 American Federation of Teachers Convention, The Progressive Caucus, and the United Action Caucus, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Bulletin: American Federation of Teachers in Action, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - American Federation of Teachers On Campus: A Newsletter for AFT College Leaders, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - American Federation of Teachers Washington Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Seattle Teacher Representation: Bulletins and Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Press and Newsletters: California Federation of Teachers, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Collective Bargaining Representation Election: Seattle Alliance of Educators Campaign Materials and Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Collective Bargaining Representation Election: Seattle Federation of Teachers Campaign Materials, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Collective Bargaining Representation Election: Official Papers (1 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Collective Bargaining Representation Election: Official Papers (2 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Publication by Seattle Public Schools: Guide, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Seattle Teachers Association: Newsletters and Mailings: Contract Negotiations, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Seattle Teachers Association: Newsletters and Mailings: Legislative Reports and Levy Promotion, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Publication: the National Caucus of Labor Committees: New Solidarity, 1971 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Mailings to Members: Seattle Teachers Association, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Publications: Seattle Public Schools: Report Card to Parents; Staff Report, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Press, Newsletters, and Contract: Seattle Community College, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Petitions Against Replacing Teachers with Paraprofessionals at Rainier Beach High School, 1971 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Publications and Mailers to Staff of Seattle Public Schools, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Publication by the Seattle School Board: Highlights, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - Correspondence and Broschure from the Washington Teachers Union; Elections Posters, 1969 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - Publication by Yakima Valley College Federation of Teachers: AFT Local 1485: The Reformer, 1969 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Correspondence to Members: Representation Competition, 1969 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Tacoma Federation of Teachers Newsletters, 1969 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Publication: Seattle Schools, 1969 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Publication: Seattle Schools, 1969 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Bulletin: State Superintendent, 1969 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications, Press, Reports, Correspondence, Minutes, and Proceedings (1 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications, Press, Reports, Correspondence, Minutes, and Proceedings (2 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications, Press, Reports, Correspondence, Minutes, and Proceedings (3 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Newsletters: Everett and Bellingham Federations of Teachers, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - The American Teacher Magazine; National and Statewide Teacher Salary Surveys, 1947-1958 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Newsletters, 1969 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Outlook - Wallingford-University Newspaper, 1970 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Press Releases, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Publication: Seattle Public Schools: Guide, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Publication: Seattle Public Schools: Guide, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Representation Elections Materials; Member Mailers from the Seattle and Everett Federations of Teachers, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - American Federation of Teachers Convention Mail Ballot, 1974 (Box-folder 6/11)
- American Federation of Teachers Local 200 records, 1964-1982; 1909-005; 4.03 cubic feet 4 boxes 1 vertical file
  Bulk of records reflect activities of the Seattle Federation of Teachers, a subgroup within the American Federation of Teachers Local 200. Records include correspondence, minutes, financial records, membership lists, publications, contract enforcement documents, convention papers, subject files, files on individual schools within the Seattle School District, and papers from various committees and subgroups within the Seattle Federation of Teachers between the years of 1964 and 1982.
  Seattle Federation of Teachers, December 21, 1982.
  - CONSTITUTION AND BY-LAWS, 1972-1973; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Constitutions, By-Laws, and Organizational Broschure: Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1969-1980; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/2-1/22)
    - Seattle Public Schools: Board Correspondence and Leaflets, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Seattle Public Schools: Administrative Correspondence and Contract Negotiations, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Correspondence: John S. Rundberg, Seattle Teachers Association Member, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Press and Correspondence: King County Labor Council, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Correspondence and Mailings: Seattle Teachers Association, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Field Representative's File: Termination of Stanton C. Bloom, Director of Organization at the Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1971 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Correspondence: Seattle Federation of Teachers Executive Board, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Correspondence and Leaflets: Dues and Payroll Deduction, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Correspondence, Elections, and Reports: Washington State Labor Council, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Correspondence: Washington Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Correspondence: Kenneth Warren, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Correspondence: Organizer Sally F. Jarrett, Field Representative/Membership, Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1976 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Dues Cancellations: Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Correspondence: Strikes, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Correspondence: American Federation of Teachers, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Correspondence Regarding Levy to Fund Schools: Kenneth R. Warren, President, Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1971-1971 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Resignation Letters: Seattle Federation of Teachers Executive Board and King County Labor Council, 1974-1974 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Correspondence: Seattle Federation of Teachers: Action Coalition for Equity Education, 1976-1976 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Strike Support: Operating Engineers Union Local 609 vs. Seattle Public Schools, District No. 1, 1975-1975 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - MINUTES, 1968-1979; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/23-2/4)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board and Regular Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1972 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes, Financial Statements, and Analysis of Membership Statistics: Executive Board, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1973 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1974 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes, Financial Statements, and Analysis of Membership Statistics: Executive Board, 1975 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1976 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1978 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1977 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Meeting Minutes: Executive Board, 1979 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 1/34)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1967-1982; SERIES IV (Box-folder 2/5-2/55)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Ledger, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Financial Statements, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Check Register, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Budgets and Financial Statements, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Collective Bargaining Campaign Financial Records, 1971 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Elections/Referenda Procedures, circa 1971 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Vote on Dues Increase: Seattle Federation of Teachers, 1973 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Legal Defense Fund, 1975 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Constitution, By-Laws, and Constitutional Revisions Committee Report, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Leaflets: Dues Collection and Increase, 1973 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Contact List: Seattle Federation of Teachers Executive Board, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Financial Statements, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Quarterly Financial Reports to the American Federation of Teachers, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Statements and Correspondence: Stock: Federated American Insurance Company, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Statements and Correspondence: Loan: First National Bank of Washington, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: List of Dropped Memberships, 1973 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - 'New Course of Action' for Seattle Federation of Teachers: Levy, Salaries, Political Action, and Contract Negotiations Strategies and Leaflets, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Budget Projections, Proposals, and Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Budgets: Norman Ferris, Treasurer, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Financial Statements, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Insurance: Albert H. Wohlers & Co. Insurance; Monumental Life Insurance Company, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: New Dues Payment System: Preauthorized Check Draft, 1975 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from Consolidated Press Incorporated, 1976 (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices for Postage Meter Rental: Pitney Bowes, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Cash Receipts, 1973 (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/31)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices, Agreements, and Reposession Correspondence for Postage Meter Rental: Pitney Bowes, Inc. and United States Leasing Corporation, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from Seattle Public Schools, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from North Seattle Printing Company, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 2/34)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from Poineer Business Forms, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 2/35)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Invoices from Ruggles Inc., Modern Office Interiors and Supplies, 1973 (Box-folder 2/36)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Employee Earnings Statement Booklets, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 2/37)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Loan from Peoples National Bank Guaranteed by American Federation of Teachers, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2/38)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Dues Collection through Bank Cards, 1973 (Box-folder 2/39)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Account with Liberty Bank of Seattle, circa 1972-circa 1980 (Box-folder 2/40)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Legal Defense Fund, 1971 (Box-folder 2/41)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Fundraising: Blank Debentures, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2/42)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Revised Financial Statements, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 2/43)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Marjorie Stern Salary Issue, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 2/44)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Loan: Peoples National Bank of Washington, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 2/45)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Attendance Rosters for Strike Meetings, 1978 (Box-folder 2/46)
    - Reports on Joint Talks: Seattle Federation of Teachers and Seattle Teachers Association, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2/47)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Ballots on Dues Raise, 1982 (Box-folder 2/48)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Financial Documents, Minutes, and Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 2/49)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Employee Earnings Documents, 1967 (Box-folder 2/50)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Tax Documents, 1971 (Box-folder 2/51)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Tax Documents, 1970 (Box-folder 2/52)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Tax Documents, 1969 (Box-folder 2/53)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Tax Documents, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2/54)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Policies, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 2/55)
  - MEMBERSHIP, 1971-1976; SERIES V (Box-folder 2/56-oversize folder; 3/1)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Membership Drive, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2/56)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Membership and Delegate Rosters, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 2/57)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Executive Board Rosters, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 2/58)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Master Membership List, 1976 (Box-folder oversize folder)
    - List of Building Representatives, with Piece about Hamilton Middle School Representative Sandy Chock, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - PUBLICATIONS, 1966-1980; SERIES VI (Box-folder 3/2-3/27)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletter and Federation Focus Bulletin, 1966 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters: Agency Shop Controversy, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1974 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Press Releases, Reports, Newsletters, Memoranda, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1975 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1977 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Press Releases, Reports, Newsletters, Memoranda and Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1971-1980 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Press Releases, Reports, Newsletters, Memoranda and Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1971-1980 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Press Releases, Reports, Newsletters, Memoranda and Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1971-1980 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Leadership Conference and Program for Progress, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers Publication: The Seattle Teacher, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Newsletters, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Action, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publication Drafts, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - American Federation of Teachers: Publication: Membership Newsletter, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Action, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Publications: Action, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: News Releases, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Seattle Federation of Teachers: Proposals to the Executive Council of the American Federation of Teachers, 1976 (Box-folder 3/23)